<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IMMIBLOGGHENICLOUD</title>
    <link>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IMMIBLOGGHENICLOUD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aria Automation - Prices without Pricing Cards</title>
      <link>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/aria-automation-prices-without-pricing-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/aria-automation-prices-without-pricing-cards/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Intro Recently, I was asked to create several Blueprints that would display the resource price at the time of the request through the Service Broker. This had to be accomplished without using VMware Aria Automation Pricing Cards.
The need was to showcase templates with these features:
Template Azure OS: Windows And Linux 3 Flavours: Small, Medium and Large Managed or Unamanged Machine (SLA) In case the vm is managed you have Monitoring SLA - STD or H24 Template GCP OS: Windows And Linux 3 Flavours: Small, Medium And Large Managed or Unamanged Machine (SLA) In case the vm is managed you have Monitoring SLA - STD or H24 Template vCenter Windows OS: Windows 2019 or 2022 3 Flavours: Small, Medium And Large Managed or Unamanged Machine In case the vm is managed you have Monitoring SLA - STD or H24 The price varies depending on the Flavour, the operating system, whether it is Managed or Unmanaged, and the type of SLA if the VM is managed.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCCM collections</title>
      <link>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/sccm-collections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 10:38:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/sccm-collections/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Intro These are various queries to populate the collections in SCCM, which will be updated in the future.
Additionally, at the bottom, I have included a script for the automatic addition of the collections shown in this post
Collections Collection Boundary Groups Based This query adds the devices that are part of a specific Boundary Group to the collection. It&#39;s necessary to modify the query by inserting the name of your own group.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a connection entry to RDM Vault on new vm deployment</title>
      <link>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/add-a-connection-entry-to-rdm-vault-on-new-vm-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 12:56:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/add-a-connection-entry-to-rdm-vault-on-new-vm-deployment/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Remote Desktop Manager is a fantastic tool for centralized management of various accesses to VMs and services. I have personally always used RDM to save the RDP and SSH connections that I most frequently used.
This tool, when used in conjunction with Devolutions Server (DVLS), is excellent for teams that need a centralized and common repository for access.
Recently, I found myself in need of automating the creation of entries within the various Vaults inside DVLS to reduce the effort caused by adding them manually.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
