<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VRO on IMMIBLOGGHENICLOUD</title>
    <link>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/tags/vro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VRO on IMMIBLOGGHENICLOUD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 12:46:49 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/tags/vro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aria Automation - Prices without price cards</title>
      <link>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/aria-automation-prices-without-price-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 12:46:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/aria-automation-prices-without-price-cards/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Intro Recentemente mi è stato richiesto di creare alcuni Blueprint e mostrare il prezzo della risorsa al momento della richiesta attraverso il service broker. Questo senza avere la possibilità di utilizzare le pricing cards di VMware Aria Automation.
La necessità era quella di mostrare template con queste caratteristiche:
Template Azure OS: Windows And Linux 3 Flavours: Small, Medium and Large Managed or Unamanged Machine (SLA) In case the vm is managed you have Monitoring SLA - STD or H24 Template GCP OS: Windows And Linux 3 Flavours: Small, Medium And Large Managed or Unamanged Machine (SLA) In case the vm is managed you have Monitoring SLA - STD or H24 Template vCenter Windows OS: Windows 2019 or 2022 3 Flavours: Small, Medium And Large Managed or Unamanged Machine In case the vm is managed you have Monitoring SLA - STD or H24 Il prezzo varia a seconda del Flavour, del sistema operativo, dal fatto che sia Managed o Unamanged e dal tipo di SLA in caso la vm sia managed.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a connection entry to RDM Vault on new vm deployment</title>
      <link>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/add-a-connection-entry-to-rdm-vault-on-new-vm-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 12:56:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.immiblogghenicloud.cloud/posts/add-a-connection-entry-to-rdm-vault-on-new-vm-deployment/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Remote Desktop Manager is a fantastic tool for centralized management of various accesses to VMs and services. I have personally always used RDM to save the RDP and SSH connections that I most frequently used.
This tool, when used in conjunction with Devolutions Server (DVLS), is excellent for teams that need a centralized and common repository for access.
Recently, I found myself in need of automating the creation of entries within the various Vaults inside DVLS to reduce the effort caused by adding them manually.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
